const basicsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Dog'",
        answers: ["Кіт", "Собака", "Птах", "Миша"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Cat'",
        answers: ["Кінь", "Кіт", "Корова", "Риба"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Bird'",
        answers: ["Птах", "Жаба", "Змія", "Вовк"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Fish'",
        answers: ["Миша", "Риба", "Качка", "Кролик"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Horse'",
        answers: ["Слон", "Кінь", "Тигр", "Ведмідь"],
        correct: 1
    }
];

const phrasesQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Cow'",
        answers: ["Кінь", "Корова", "Вівця", "Кіт"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Sheep'",
        answers: ["Коза", "Свиня", "Вівця", "Курка"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Pig'",
        answers: ["Свиня", "Заєць", "Вовк", "Олень"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Duck'",
        answers: ["Гуска", "Качка", "Курка", "Птах"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Rabbit'",
        answers: ["Кіт", "Миша", "Кролик", "Лисиця"],
        correct: 2
    }
];

const literatureQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Lion'",
        answers: ["Тигр", "Лев", "Ведмідь", "Вовк"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Tiger'",
        answers: ["Леопард", "Лев", "Тигр", "Рись"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Bear'",
        answers: ["Вовк", "Лисиця", "Ведмідь", "Олень"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Wolf'",
        answers: ["Собака", "Вовк", "Лисиця", "Кіт"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Translate: 'Fox'",
        answers: ["Вовк", "Кіт", "Лисиця", "Миша"],
        correct: 2
    }
];
